I mean
It's just because I keep telling him not to say it and I just I just told I just told Chris and I just told
I just like and so I just have to like stick by it like others. I you know, it's unfortunate
Alex you're supposed to be like, you know, part of the you're supposed to be first of all, oh, thank you
Why I I saw you
Looking in the drawer and taking that wrench out of it. And I was like, oh, this is what I was going to play with it. No
You come and you say you can't use that. I just told Chris. I just told crystal
I know you heard I just told crystal and you just let me end the panel because she is like why did so?
Why do you say it?
You don't add it
I don't know. I don't know everyone likes it. I don't know if they'd like to they'd love to call me that I guess it's like so
It's not like it's not really nice. It's like
Imagine like it's like imagine like a white person going on a black person's show and calling them the hard are that's or just using that word, you know
and
It's probably they probably would not take too kindly to it, right?
I mean, I really don't care about it, but I care because I just made a rule, no hate speech.
And I consider that kind of under the derogatory terms, right?
Maybe one of the last acceptable ones to some people, but it's not.
It's just not it's not it's not the language. I want much. I like to have I think I better gave people here
Most gave people are terrified to come here. They don't they think it's like a hostile environment
And it's like I I kind of can thrive in a hostile environment, but you know a lot of a lot of gay people can but
A lot of gay people were probably just like, you know, fuck this shit like
So I don't know just be you got out and I know yeah, I know there's not like really
Like that
Like kind of like hateful race and there might be like a little a few people that are like actually hatefully racist or something like that
But I don't think most even the people that use the word I just think people just like get a kick out of like
being shocking and edgy and
Trying to be funny or something. I don't think the words funny. I don't think they're funny words. I just think they're kind of like
This tastes like I don't like them
So this is don't use them just pretend that I pretend like I'm standing right there and
I actually do care if the word said just pretend like you know
Think about pretend pretend like it would break my heart if I heard you say that
I mean, of course it doesn't but just pretend and then so don't say it just think about it just it would break my heart if you know
you know
The show is far I'm not about the word. Okay. It doesn't care about the word. I care about the show. Okay, you get it
We're gay chance. What does that mean? Oh, yeah
Well, I see what these are you start talking Latin on my panel and everything goes to fucking hell
You can't you say Latin wrong fucking goats up here. I mean Jesus
Stop saying Latin on my show
Can we get a vagina? I guess I don't know Alex your letter out of your land wasn't perfect. God your lens pretty good. Okay?
So I think I'm I will get some food tonight, but
No, I mean yeah, I know it's like a little expensive, but it doesn't take open right now
I'm not walking anywhere
I'm a streamer. I have to have you know stuff brought me once in a while. Okay, here we go
I should charge Alice for dinner because the asshole I'm having at my stream
Taco Bell, maybe
Well, they said I talk about there's a free drink, but it's like a dragon fruit juice or something a little more of a coffee kind of
Mm-hmm
Offers
Hey at the Buffalo Wild Wings $5.00 at $15.00. That sounds pretty good deal
Check that they have coffee will be sold
Dipping sauces come on coffee. Oh, they don't have it. Okay, never mind
Michelle's house of waffles and pancakes. $3 off
It's not like Mexican food
Dragon fruit juice is delicious. Yeah, I mean if it's like I like like some Starbucks like real
But it's like I don't think Taco Bell has like just a flavor in it. I'm not sure if it's like authentic dragon fruit
Sounds good to you guys. Baha blasted me from this. Hey, Goddy
They have this recipe called dirty little vegan I can't even show it the paper pictures just to
This help here. I am these pictures is this to these two buns
But they're like put really close together so it looks like a bud or boobs or something
This is three little vegan and I can't even show it on my show because people say oh my god someone's showing the butt
That's kind of I'm gonna look at the door dash. There's no good deals on
We've got to say no Somalian we're back or back you calling me Somalian
Oh, hold on.
Who's Somalian?
Oh, yeah, that's, you know, actually,
Yassin is the Somalian,
the director actually is the Somalian on the show.
Hit the bell, are you kidding me, guys?
Yeah, if I can do that.
Alex, Alex.
Make it make it oath right in the chat. You will see you will not remember you said earlier
I said don't say can't stop won't stop and you're really I'll never say it again
Okay, so just forget about that you can say can't stop won't stop you can have that back you can say any time you want don't say
the n word
F-A-G-G-O-T and don't call
Unless you have the relationship with them where they where you know them don't just call it
Any random woman on the panel the UNC or the SECH and stuff like that
I know I know yes, they'd be able to promise that you won't say that you won't say the derogatory terms though
You can say you can't stop once you can't say the derogatory terms
And those empty thread gotty. I mean, I'm like this I'm this close
That's not making him pledge Alex get the pledge it or your wrench has gone in like probably one minute
If they pledge in the chat, you won't say those words again. Oh
I'm you said you IPO
There's a kind of beer Alice. I was yeah, Alex. You know type it right. Okay her. Oh, you probably case this one
Okay
You're close there's got one second left
Hey Vicky, baby
Yeah, but you know
I do appreciate you know, I appreciate anybody bringing anybody here with our trolls or not
You know, but I do hope that they would respect the chat
I know dogs. Just you know, just just behave in the chat. You're told are welcome here. It's just I
Need them to kind of like
Behave a little bit. I know they never will but
But I have to use this ever whip. I'm gonna I have to get a whip now
That's the start whipping the trolls and they get too close
And then I mean it's not it's just like it's not like it's hard. He's called car car for you. Okay. Hey, they're punky, okay?
Pull a card for punky
Pull it up. I got one car for you. I'm seeing your car. Hold on. Oh, it's bunk. Spunky. I'll put your car. Hold on
come down
Your car. Hey there, punky is
Oh
Ace of pentacles and we just get the ace of pentacles earlier. We can see it's that
That is the jungle book that the lion from the jungle book or something. He's like he's a key or a little come
So there's a coin, so it's being handed to them, and so maybe you're buying or selling
something, but I would say this is an investment, I think more, there's some kind of investment
being made, and this coin is being handed down, and it should go into something bigger,
but it's like a seed, you need to take care of it and plant it wisely, right?
Because big opportunities are heading your way whether you're given a lucrative new role or exciting offer
with a list of a lot of potential or
Use or use some upon hidden treasures
The ace of coins advise you take full advantage of the situation
Okay
enjoy
You like that
That's your face and just okay. You're welcome
Is everyone's you and yeah, I thought I ordered my food. I'm gonna get the pin my leg and did it
So what's up, so
What was about to happen
He he made a face. What was that like five minutes behind?
You can't he brought he's gonna say it or you just sit backstage looking cute say what?
He and he ever bombs sometimes we are not to say it. Yeah
where we were we're not saying you just put all these promises for the rules and
it's like so it says no no right no like fine but every day there's new rules
no no no I've had this after the same bear ever the same rule bear I'll put it
up right there it's the same rule let's go over the rules let's go over the rules
no threats we never threaten yeah okay hate speech what was that until
No, I don't I don't do that. Okay. No doxing. I never dox playing music. I slipped a few times
Honestly, yeah, I could I could admit to slipping on the music. Okay. I'll be better. No, I've slanted a few
never nudity
Even though you blame me for some nipslip. I never did that and respect the host. I can't I can't agree to that one fuck
Oh my god. Oh my gosh. Hey, it's it's uh, it's what's what's his name be Z. Oh, QQ. Yeah, thank you
No, Stephanie. It's her name is funky. I'm sorry. Yeah, that's a good friend of mine. Okay. Okay, sorry
So you're not allowed to say nigger on here. Oh my god